And now, just as we did with our sliders,
现在就像滑块流程那样
let's go ahead and update our UdaciSteppers component.
我们更新下 UdaciSteppers 组件
So, in UdaciSteppers, we're going to need a few different things.
在 UdaciSteppers 中 我们将需要添加几项不同的内容
These are going to be buttons,
它们将是按钮
so we will import TouchableOpacity,
导入 TouchableOpacity
and then we are also going to want to grab some icon components.
还需要获取一些图标组件
So we will grab FontAwesome as well as Entypo,
我们将获取 FontAwesome 和 Entypo
I think that's how you pronounce that.
应该就是这么读的
And both of these again come with create React Native app under expo/vector-icons.
二者都是 React Native 应用自带的 并位于 expo/vector-icons 下
And so, if you remember just like with UdaciSlider,
和 UdaciSlider 一样
we are giving UdaciSteppers value onIncrement onDecrement and everything else.
我们将在 UdaciSteppers 中为 onIncrement onDecrement 和其他一切提供值
So we can come up here and destructure it.
转到这里并进行解构
We will say max, unit, and step,
输入 max, unit, step
value onIncrement, as well as onDecrement.
value, onIncrement, onDecrement
And then what we're going to do is instead of returning the text,
我们将返回几项不同的内容
we are going to return a few different things.
而不是输出文本
The first one is going to be a Touchable component,
首先返回一个可触摸组件
and whenever we press it,
每当我们点按它时
we are going to run onDecrement.
将运行 onDecrement
Inside of here, what we're going to have is an icon,
在这里面将是一个图标
the name is going to be, minus,
名称为 minus
we'll give it a size, let's say 30,
size 设为 30
and then we will give it a color of black so that we can see it right now.
color 设为 black 以便现在就能看到
And then we also want another button here,
还需要一个按钮
but instead of decrementing,
这次不是递减
we want to increment and then instead of minus,
而是递增
what we want is plus.
名称从 minus 改为 plus
And then now, let's go ahead and wrap these in a view.
将这些封装在 View 中
So right now, what we've done is we have built both of our buttons.
我们已经构建了这两个按钮
But just like with the slider,
和滑块一样
we also want this stuff over here,
我们还需要添加这些内容
the specific value and the unit.
即具体的值和单位
So what we will do is add a bracket there and then what we will do down here,
在这里添加一个括号 然后在这里
we will have a view with two different text components inside of it.
添加一个 View 其中具有两种不同的 Text 组件
The first one is going to be the value and the second one is going to be the unit.
第一个组件将是 value 第二个将是 Unit
So now, what should happen if everything is working,
现在 如果一切正常的话
and of course, it is not.
当然存在问题
Oh, it is, we just had to refresh.
噢 只需刷新下就行了
All right, so now what we have is we have our buttons,
现在这里出现了按钮
we can press these and they will go up and they will go down.
可以点击这些按钮 它们将增大或减小